(Sheldon:)I feel no better now
than when I left.
(Amy:)But you still
accomplished something.
(Leonard:)Yeah. If you had
told anyone
(Leonard:)that you were going away
on a train by yourself
(Leonard:)across the country, do you
know what they would have said?
(Sheldon:)That I couldn't do it?
Exactly.
Right after they said, "Yay!"
(Amy:)But you did do it.
(Amy:)So what if it didn't
all go your way?
(Amy:)That's what makes it
an adventure.
(Sheldon:)That's a good point.
Yeah, I'm a lot like
Gandalf the Grey.
(Sheldon:)He fought the Balrog and emerged
(Sheldon:)stronger than ever
as Gandalf the White.
(Sheldon:)I was robbed
of my phone and pants,
(Sheldon:)and I, too,
came back stronger.
(Sheldon:)And whiter, too,
'cause I wasn't
(Sheldon:)in direct sunlight
for six weeks.
(Amy:)See? This trip
was good for you.
(Sheldon:)Indeed.
(Sheldon:)I was the world's
smartest caterpillar.
(Sheldon:)And then after pupating
in our nation's railway system,
(Sheldon:)I've burst forth
(Sheldon:)as the world's
smartest butterfly.